

tonyly.com

425-343-3711

♥ Kirkland, WA

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

SUMMARY

- · Adapts to change quickly
- Excellent team communication
- · Able to resolve team conflicts
- · Maintains patients as top priority
- Builds lasting patient trust and loyalty

Licensed pharmacist in Washington state. Possesses seven years of pharmacy experience in a community setting. Excellent interpersonal skills drives desire to build long-lasting relationships with patients, pharmacy colleagues, and fellow medical professionals. Seeking a pharmacist position that will provide the opportunity to practice high-quality, patient-centered health care.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NEW ENGLAND COLLEGE OF PHARMACY

PharmD · 2016

UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON

BS Microbiology · 2011

PROFESSIONAL LICENSURE

WASHINGTON PHARMACIST LICENSE · PH60686691

Jul 2017 to Jun 2018

IMMUNIZATION CERTIFICATE Sep 2014 to Present

EMPLOYMENT

CAREERSTAFF RX
Seattle, WA
Pharmacist Graduate Intern
Dec 2016 to Present

• Float to different pharmacy teams to provide relief in pharmacy technician roles

- · Rapidly integrate into new pharmacy teams each shift and achieve cohesive teamwork
- Frequently learn unfamiliar pharmacy software systems
- · Advocate for patients to ensure they receive appropriate treatment while minimizing costs
- · Answer clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assist in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Provide patient education on proper medication usage and common side effects

TARGET PHARMACY

Pharmacist Intern; Pharmacy Assistant

Redmond, WA Aug 2007 to Aug 2014

- Answered clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assisted in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- · Interpreted prescriptions via electronic patient profiles to minimize risk of DDIs and identify possible contraindications
- · Interprofessional collaboration with prescribers via telephone to ensure accurate and appropriate therapy to patients
- Prepared oral antibiotic suspensions for patients
- Provided patient education on proper medication usage and possible side effects

UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON, DEPT OF PHARMACEUTICS

Research Technician II (Lin Lab)

Seattle, WA Jun 2010 to Aug 2012

- Primary research in identifying endogenous biomarkers for cytochrome P450 metabolism
- Extracted compounds of interest from human biological specimen via liquid-liquid extractions
- Conducted biological sample analysis via Mass Spectrometry (HPLC/MS-MS)
- · Compiled metabolomics database using Quadrupole-Time of Flight (Q-TOF) instrumentation

PROJECTS

VANCOMYCIN THERAPEUTIC DOSING AND MONITORING PROGRAM

May 2015 to Aug 2015

Conducted retrospective outcomes evaluation on pharmacist-driven vancomycin dosing and monitoring protocols in inpatient and acute care settings. Spearheaded data analysis enhancement with pharmacy informatics integration to automate data collection.

LEADERSHIP

Phi Lambda Sigma, Delta Chi Chapter · Historian

2014 to 2015

American College of Clinical Pharmacy (ACCP), Student Chapter · Historian

2014 to 2015

American Pharmacists Association, Academy of Student Pharmacists (APhA-ASP) · Communications VP

2013 to 2014